[
  {
    "question": "Servers are computers that provide resources to other computers connected to a",
    "choice1": "Client",
    "choice2": "Mainframe",
    "choice3": "Supercomputer",
    "choice4": "Network",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "A program that is used to view websites is called a",
    "choice1": "Browser",
    "choice2": "Web viewer",
    "choice3": "Spreadsheet",
    "choice4": "Word processor",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of broadband internet connection?",
    "choice1": "Satellite",
    "choice2": "DSL",
    "choice3": "Dial up",
    "choice4": "Cable",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for unsolicited Email?",
    "choice1": "Spam",
    "choice2": "Backbone",
    "choice3": "Usenet",
    "choice4": "News group",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Rules for exchanging data between computers are called",
    "choice1": "Procedures",
    "choice2": "Protocols",
    "choice3": "Hyperlinks",
    "choice4": "Programs",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is the basic communication language or protocol of the internet",
    "choice1": "TCP/IP",
    "choice2": "TCDP/IEP",
    "choice3": "TCMP/IKP",
    "choice4": "TCTP/ITP",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Documents converted to ____ can be published to the web",
    "choice1": "Doc file",
    "choice2": "machine language",
    "choice3": "http",
    "choice4": "HTML",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a means of personal communication on the internet?",
    "choice1": "E-mail",
    "choice2": "Instanotes",
    "choice3": "Instant messaging",
    "choice4": "Chat",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following cannot be a part of an E-mail address?",
    "choice1": "Underscore (_)",
    "choice2": "Space ( )",
    "choice3": "At sign (@)",
    "choice4": "Period (-)",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which term identifies a specific computer on the web and the main page of the entire site?",
    "choice1": "WWW",
    "choice2": "Link",
    "choice3": "SQL",
    "choice4": "URL",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The two basic parts of URLs are",
    "choice1": "TCP and FTP",
    "choice2": "The protocol and the domain name",
    "choice3": "TCP/IP and ISP",
    "choice4": "Destination and device",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Generally to send data from a local computer to a remote computer/internet is called?",
    "choice1": "Download",
    "choice2": "Upload",
    "choice3": "Editing",
    "choice4": "E-mail",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The process of communicating with a file from a terminal is",
    "choice1": "Heuristic",
    "choice2": "Interactive",
    "choice3": "Interrogation",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Portion of server memory set aside to temporary hold data packets form workstations is called",
    "choice1": "Dirty packet buffer",
    "choice2": "Packet cache buffer",
    "choice3": "Packet block",
    "choice4": "Packet receive buffer",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The most common method for gaining access to the internet is through a",
    "choice1": "Point-to-point computer",
    "choice2": "Virtual provider or computer",
    "choice3": "Provider or host computer",
    "choice4": "Dumb terminal",
    "answer": 3
  }
]